Let's start with the process for warm transferring the caller,
no questions asked.
Thank you for calling member services.
My name is Natasha.
May I have your first and last name,
please?
Hi,
will you please transfer me to the enhanced member support unit?
Yes,
absolutely.
I'd be happy to transfer you over.
Do you mind if I place you on a brief hold for just a moment?
No problem.
Thank you.
One moment,
please.
Navigate to the phone panel to place the caller on hold.
Once the caller is on hold,
select the warm transfer tab,
then search EMSU in the search bar.
Select the correct transfer number from the list
and press the green call button.
Wait for the EMSU agent to answer.
Thank you for calling
Enhanced member support unit.
Hi there,
I have a caller that requested to be transferred to EMSU.
Do you have their name or any additional information about the caller?
I do not.
OK,
go ahead and complete the transfer now.
thank you.
Click the transfer button in the phone panel to complete the warm transfer.